(knocking)
쉘든이 와이파이
비번 또 바꿨나?
Hi. Did Sheldon change
the Wi-Fi password again?
'페니는 밥도 얻어 먹으니
공짜 와이파이는 안돼'로 바꿨어
Yeah, it's
"Penny already eats our food.
She can pay for Wi-Fi."
공백 없이
No spaces.
Okay.
지금까지 계속 얻어 먹었는데
If you can't get me
to stop eating your food,
와이파이라고 못 쓸거 같아?
what makes you think you can
get me to stop using your Wi-Fi?
넌 변할 수 있다고 믿어
I believe that you're capable
of great change.
이제는 '발렌타임'이라
잘못 말하지 않잖아
Like when I finally got you
to stop saying "Valentimes Day""
이상한 얘기 들려줄까?
You want to hear
something weird?
그래
Sure.
2000년에 요한 바오로 2세가
할렘 농구단 명예 선수가 됐어
In the year 2000,
Pope John Paul II was named
an honorary Harlem Globetrotter.
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
페니한테 이상한 얘기 해준다며
You asked Penny if she wanted
to hear something weird.
응, 내가 할 말이 있다고
Yeah, because I have
something weird to tell her.
Oh.
게임인 줄 알았지
I thought it was a game.
하려던 얘기가 뭔데?
What's yours?
지미 스페커맨이라는 애가 있는데
There's this guy,
Jimmy Speckerman,
고등학교 때
날 엄청 괴롭혔지
who used to torment me
in high school.
페이스북 쪽지가 왔더라고
He sent me a message
through Facebook.
만나서 한 잔 하재
He's in town
and wants to have drinks.
만약 이게 게임이었다면
뭘 고를래?
Okay, Penny, if it were a game,
here are your choices.
옛친구로부터 온 이메일 혹은
An e-mail
from an old acquaintance,
종교지도자가 재즈곡에 맞춰
선보이는 슬램덩크 묘기?
or the head of one of the
largest religious institutions
in the world slam dunking
to "Sweet Georgia Brown." Pick.
안 고르면 피곤해
Just do it,
'cause he's not gonna let it go.
농구 교황
Basketball Pope.
그럼, 그래야지
And that's how it's done.
그래서 넌 어떡할 건데?
What are you gonna do
about your bully?
- 깡패는 만날 생각이야?
- 모르겠어
- Are you gonna see him?
- I don't know.
네가 마시던 하와이안
펀치에 오줌 싼 애야?
Is this the fellow who peed
in your Hawaiian Punch?
아니, 그건 다른 애였어
No, that was a different guy.
바지를 너무 세게 들어올려
Was he the one
who wedgied you so hard,
고환이 윗쪽으로
당겨지게 만든 애야?
your testicle reascended,
크리스마스 내내 고환이
내려오길 기다려야 했잖아
and you spent
your whole Christmas break
waiting for it
to come back down?
아니, 그것도 다른 애였어
No, that was
a different, different guy.
네 머리로
호두를 깨려던 애야?
Was he the one who used
your head to open a nut?
아니
No.
Oh, oh, oh.
그럼 겨드랑이 털을
억지로 먹인 애?
Was he the one
who made you eat your arm hair?
그건 이 자식 누나였어
No, but, actually,
that was this guy's sister.
만나서 어쩌자는 걸까?
All right, well,
what do you think he wants?
몰라
I don't know.
곧 연말이 다가오잖아
You know, the holidays
are just around the corner.
반대쪽 고환도
당겨주려는 거 아닐까?
Maybe he wants to see
if he can lodge
the other testicle up there.
그건 다른 놈이 한 짓이라고
I told you.
That was a different guy.
아쉽다
Hmm. That's too bad.
We could have spent
공이 떨어지길 기다리면서
새해를 맞이하고 싶었는데
New Year's Eve waiting
for the ball to drop.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x11
The Speckerman Recurrence
Original Air Date on December 8, 2011
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
(classical fanfare plays
on computer)
새벽 2시인데 안 자?
It's 2:00 a.m.
What are you doing up?
스톡홀름에서 노벨상
시상식 생방 중이야
Nobel Prize acceptance ceremony
streaming live from Stockholm.
올해는 과학자들이
뭘 입었는지 궁금하겠네
Sure. You want to see
what all the scientists
are wearing this year.
이 사람들 좀 봐
Look at these men.
과학 분야에서 제일
명예로운 상을 받았어
They've managed to win the top
science prize in the world
초기 우주 팽창에 대한
양자 이론의 이해력이
with no more understanding
of the quantum underpinnings
of the expansion
of the early universe
신이 거위에게 선사한
수준과 비슷한데 말야
than God gave a goose.
너도 보면 좋을 걸
You should pay attention,
Leonard.
언젠가는 너도
오를 수 있는 무대야
Someday this could be you
up there.
고마워
Thanks.
So,
너는 왜 안 자는데?
what's got you up?
상한 조개라도 먹었어?
Did you have a bad clam?
조개 안 먹었어
I didn't have clams.
널 24시간 지켜보지 않으니
I don't watch you
24 hours a day.
뭘 하는지 당연히 모르지
I don't know what you do.
지미 때문에 그래
It's this Jimmy Speckerman
thing.
만나야 할지 모르겠어
I can't decide if I should
agree to see him or not.
지난 번 만났을 때
안 좋은 추억이 있어
Of course that might be
because the last time
I ran into him,
운동화끈을 치실처럼
쓰게 만들었거든
he made me floss
with my own shoelaces.
끈 없는 로퍼를 신어
Wear loafers.
저기 사울 펄무터 좀 봐라
Look at Dr. Saul
Perlmutter up there,
노벨상을 꼭 끌어 안았네
clutching that Nobel Prize.
왜 그래, 사울?
What's the matter, Saul?
누가 훔칠까봐?
You afraid someone's
going to steal it?
네가 아인슈타인의
우주 상수를 훔친 것처럼?
Like you stole Einstein's
cosmological constant?
You know what?
공포에 떨며 살고 싶지 않아
I am tired of living
in fear of this guy.
만나서 할 말은 해야겠어
I'm gonna go see
him and finally say
고등학교 때
못 했던 말들도
all the things I should
have said in high school.
덩치만 크면 다야?
You know, "Pick on
someone your own size""
넌 우리 엄마랑 섹스한 적 없어
"You did not have sex
with my mother."
그래, 내 자신을 때리는
내가 바보같다는 거 알아
And "Yes, I do know why
I'm hitting myself."
펄무터가 왕이랑
악수를 하고 있어
Oh, now Perlmutter's
shaking the king's hand.
시계 조심해, 구스타프
Yeah, check for your watch,
Gustaf.
소매치기 당할 수도 있어
He might have lifted it.
너무 예쁜 드레스다
I love this dress.
그 동안 왜 안 입었어?
How come I never
see you wear it?
내가 입으면 셔츠가 되거든
'Cause when I wear it,
it's a shirt.
하워드는 오늘 뭐해?
So, what's Howard
doing tonight?
레너드랑 학교 깡패를
상대하러 갔어
Oh, they all went with Leonard
to confront his childhood bully.
잘됐네
Oh, terrific.
고등학교 쿼터백에 맞서는
네 명의 수학 선수들
High school quarterback
against four mathletes.
레너드가 돌아오면
When Leonard gets back,
세로토닌 수치를 재고 싶어
I'd love to check
his serotonin levels.
주사기 한 통 정도의
피를 뽑게 허락해줄까?
Do you think he'd let me draw
a syringe full of his blood?
바늘을 별로 안 좋아하는데
Hmm, he's not crazy
about needles,
조깅을 시키면 코에서
피가 뿜어나올 거야
but if you get him to go
jogging,
it'll just pour out of his nose.
날 괴롭히던 여자는
만날 용기가 없어
I don't think
I can meet the girl
who was always mean to me.
태미 보드닉
Tammy Bodnick.
체육 시간 때 탈의실에서
내 옷을 다 훔치고
One time
while I was in gym class,
she stole all my clothes
엘프 의상만 남겨뒀더라
and left an elf costume
in my locker.
저런
Oh, that's awful.
나한테 너무 큰 사이즈였어
Worst part was, it was too big.
그 정도는 약과지
That's nothing.
중3 때 애들이 핸드로션에
발모제를 넣었어
In ninth grade, the girls put
Rogaine in my hand lotion.
6개월 내에
별명이 여러 개 생겼지
Within six months, the
nicknames began to fly.
'고릴라 핑거 파울러'가
제일 가슴 아팠어
I think the one that hurt the
most was Gorilla Fingers Fowler.
(sighs)
불쌍해라
Wow. You poor thing.
넌 어때?
What about you?
Oh.
모르겠어,
난 운이 좋았나봐
I don't know. I guess
my school was a nice place.
우리 학교는 그런 게 없었어
We didn't really have bullies.
별명을 지어서 놀리거나
Come on, no one ever
gave anyone mean nicknames
이유 없이 괴롭힌 적이 없다고?
or picked on them or put gum
in their hairy knuckles
난 손가락에 껌이 붙어서
피넛버터로 떼어내야 했는데
so the school nurse had to use
peanut butter to get it out?
우리는 그런 적 없어
No, we weren't really like that.
장난을 친 적은 있어도
I mean, look, we played pranks
on each other,
못되게 군 적은 없어
but it was never mean.
캐시라고 성적이
좋은 애가 있었는데
Like, okay,
this one girl, Kathy Geiger,
got really good grades,
so we blindfolded her,
눈을 가린 채 묶어놓고
하루밤을 밭에서 보내게 했어
tied her up and left her
in a cornfield overnight.
끔찍하다
Oh, my God,
that's awful.
아냐, 재밌어서
모두 웃었어
No, it was funny.
Everyone laughed.
캐시도 웃었니?
Did Kathy
Geiger laugh?
그건 잘 모르겠다
Uh, probably.
It's hard to say.
옥수수로 입을 막았거든
She kind of had an ear
of corn in her mouth.
털보 손가락 파울러가
깡패랑 친구가 될 줄은 몰랐네
Who would have thought
Fuzzy Fingers Fowler
is best friends with a bully?
뭐?
깡패라니
What? I was not a bully.
그렇게 들리는 걸
Kind of sounds like you were.
흉악범인 것 같기도
And maybe a felon.
옥수수 밭에 가기 싫으면
가만히 있어
Shh. That's how you
wind up in a cornfield.
저쪽에 있는 남자인가?
Is that him over there?
아니
No.
그럼 저쪽은?
How about that guy?
널 싫어할 것처럼 생겼어
He looks like he'd hate you.
이봐, 혼자 둬도 괜찮다니까
You know, I can really do this
by myself.
널 응원하러 왔어
Hey, we're here
to support you, buddy.
아니, 그런 것 같지 않아
No, you're not.
You're here to see
머리통이 속옷으로
덮히는 걸 구경하러 왔겠지
if I get my underwear
pulled over my head.
속옷을 입었어?
멍청이
(laughing):
You wore underwear? You fool.
무슨 말 할지 생각했어?
So, have you figured out what
you're going to say to him?
사과하게 만들 거야
You bet. I am going to
make him apologize
학창 시절에
날 괴롭힌 것에 대해
for all the crap
he pulled on me in school.
꽤 긴 리스트네
That's quite a list.
뭐라고 쓴 건지 모르겠다
I can't read your handwriting.
무슨 단어야?
What's that word?
음낭
"Scrotum."
이건?
What's that one?
스테이플러
Uh, "stapled."
레너드
Leonard.
(laughing)
Oh, hi.
야, 만나서 만갑다
Holy crap, man,
it's good to see you.
이쪽은 쉘든, 라지,
그리고 하워드야
Yeah. You, too.
Uh, Jimmy, this is
Sheldon and Raj and Howard.
여기 맥주 좀 주세요
Hi. Fellas... Hey,
can I get a beer?
많이 컸네
Wow. Look at you.
꼬마 레너드 호프스태더
Little Leonard Hofstadter.
잘 나가는 과학자라며
I hear
you're a big-time scientist now.
한방 먹었네
And there's the first
zinger. Ouch.
그럭저럭 지내고 있지
I'm doing okay, I guess.
무슨 대학에서
물리학자라고 들었어
Okay? Come on, I read online
you're a physicist
at a university,
상도 탔다며
you won some medal.
뉴콤 메달이야
The Newcomb medal.
축하해
Yeah, congratulations.
축하?
Congratulations?
겨우 뉴콤 메달에?
The Newcomb medal?
Oh, please.
숙제에 '참 잘했어요'
도장을 받는 수준이야
That's the scientific equivalent
of a smiley face sticker
on your homework.
아무튼 대단해
From what I read,
it sounded like a big deal.
레너드가 이렇게
비난 당하는데
Oh, good Lord,
are we going to stand here
가만히 듣고만 있을 거야?
and listen to him
tear Leonard apart like this?
나도 뉴콤 메달
받은 적 있어
Hey, I won a Newcomb medal, too.
내 말이
My point.
예전에 얼마나 작았는지
You should have seen this guy
back in the day.
아무데나 잘 들어가더라고
Huh? He was so little, he could
fit in just about anywhere.
락커, 쓰레기통
Lockers, trash cans.
야, 그 백팩에는
어떻게 들어갔냐?
Oh, man, how did you get
inside that backpack?
혼자 힘으로 한 건 아니지
Oh, I can't take all the credit.
너도 많이 도왔잖아
You helped a lot.
Yeah.
우리는 개그 팀 같았어
We were practically
a comedy team.
흑사병과 유럽처럼
Like the Black Death
and Europe.
지미, 왜 날 보자고
했는지 궁금해
Jimmy, I'm kind of curious why
you wanted to see me.
Okay, here it is.
생각해둔 돈벌이가 있어
I have this great
money-making idea.
구상은 했는데엔지니어가 필요해
I just need a gear head
to get it to the finish line.
엔지니어라면 하워드지
Technically, Howard's the
gear head.
레너드는 그냥
동네 레이저 자키야
Leonard's just a dime store
laser jockey.
아이디어가 뭔데?
What's the idea?
비밀로 하는 거지?
This is just between us, right?
응, 그래
- Right.
- Okay.
어떤 영화든 3D 감상을
가능하게 만드는 안경이야
What do you think
about a pair of glasses
that makes any movie
you want into 3D?
멋진 생각이다
That sounds amazing.
내가 제일 먼저
보고 싶은 건 '애니'야
First movie I'm
watching-- Annie.
어떻게 작동하는데?
How exactly would
these glasses work?
그건 나야 모르지,그래서 공돌이가 필요해
How the hell should I know?
That's why I need a nerd.
불가능할 것 같아
I don't think something like
that's even possible.
넌 할 수 있어
Aw, come on, you can
figure it out.
내가 아는 애들 중
제일 똑똑하잖아
You're like the smartest
guy I've ever known.
제일 똑똑하다고?
The smartest...?!
이봐, 비꼬는 것도
정도껏 해야지
All right, you know,
I may not have
a firm grasp on sarcasm, but
even I know that was a doozy.
레너드, 넌 계속
무서워할 이유가 없어
Leonard, you can't live in
fear of this man forever.
쉘든, 내가 알아서 할게
Sheldon, I got this.
못하고 있잖아
You clearly don't.
내 줏대없는 친구가
하려던 말을 대신할게
What my spineless friend
lacks the courage to say
넌 못된 사람이야
is you're a
terrible person
레너드의 작은 사이즈
who took advantage
뒤떨어진 운동 신경
of his tiny size,
his uncoordinated nature
그리고 선천적 남성성
결여를 이용했잖아
and his congenital
lack of masculinity.
쉘든
Sheldon...
레너드,
난 널 친구로 사랑해
Leonard, I platonically
love you, man,
솔직히 말하면
넌 엉망이야
but face it, you're a mess.
무슨 말이야
I don't understand.
고등학교 때 너가
날 조금 괴롭혔잖아
I think what he's trying to say
is that maybe in high school
you picked on me a little bit.
조금?
A little bit?
유두에 허쉬 키세스 초콜릿을
접착제로 붙여놓았다며
The man Super Glued Hershey's
Kisses to your nipples.
유두에 받아야할 키스는
다른 종류라고
That's funny because those
aren't the kind of kisses
you want on your nipples.
그건 뭐야?
What is that?
레너드한테 벌어진
끔찍한 일들이야
This is a list of your heinous
acts against Leonard.
청소년기까지 오줌을
못 가리는 원인도 있어
One of which is certainly the
cause of him wetting his bed
well into his teens.
14살은 그래도...
아냐, 됐다
14 is not... Aw, never mind.
이건 무슨 단어야?
What's this word?
지지배
"Nancy."
넌 3년 동안 날
지지배라고 불렀어
You called me Nancy
for three years.
글씨 좀 잘 쓰는
연습을 해야겠다
You really need to work
on your penmanship.
Oh, man, I...
무슨 말을 해야할지
I don't know what to say.
난 그냥 장난이라고 생각했어
I always thought we were
just having some fun.
나는 즐겁지 않았어
It wasn't fun for me.
레너드, 너무 약해
You're being too kind, Leonard.
네가 레너드를 망쳤어
You ruined him.
가자, 얘들아
Come on, guys.
멋지다, 쉘든
That was pretty badass, dude.
난 약자를 위해 싸우지
I help the weak.
내가 배트맨과 닮은
이유 중 하나야
It's yet another way I'm
exactly like Batman.
참고로 지미 때문에
오줌을 못 가리는 거 아냐
Hey, for the record, Jimmy
wasn't the reason I wet the bed.
그건 엄마 탓이지
That one has my mother
written all over it.
고등학교 때 말을
더듬는다고 놀려서 미안
Anyway, I'm really sorry
I made fun of your
stutter in high school.
잘하고 있어
You're doing great.
Uh-huh.
제발 빨리 좀 끝내라
Oh, God, just
finish the sentence.
그럼 어쩔 수 없지,
잘 있어
Okay, well, I'm sorry
you feel that way. Bye.
아무도 사과를 안 받아줘
No one wants to hear
my apologies.
전화로 해서 그래
I think your mistake is doing it
over the phone.
직접 만나서 눈동자를
바라보면 녹을 텐데
If they could look
into your eyes, they'd melt.
페니, 과거는 중요하지 않아
Penny, it doesn't matter
what you did in the past.
넌 지금 좋은 사람이야
You're a good person now.
그렇게 쉽게 말하지 마
That's easy for you to say.
싸-싸-싸-쌍년 소리는
내가 들었으니까
You weren't just called
a "b-b-b-b-bitch."
이타주의로 죄책감을
누그러뜨리면 어떨까
Perhaps you could assuage
your guilt through altruism.
어떤 단어를 모르는 거야?
Which word's tripping you up?
'이타주의' 아니면
'누그러뜨리다'?
"Assuage," or "altruism"?
둘 다
Both.
남에게 마음을 베풀면
기분이 나아질 거야
You'll feel better by doing
something nice for someone.
- 알고 있었어
- 그럴 줄 알았어
- I actually knew that.
- I never doubted you.
난 2주에 한 번
급식소에서 봉사를 해
Every other week I serve at
a soup kitchen downtown.
그건 못해
Ooh, I can't do that.
뜨거운 솥 앞에 있으면
머리가 붕 뜨거든
If I stand over a steaming pot,
my hair just goes boing!
다른 일 없을까?
What else could I do?
어려운 사람들에게 집을
지어주는 해비타트는?
There's Habitat for Humanity--
building houses for the poor.
내 집도 마련하지 못했는데
Okay, come on, I don't even
have my own house--
남의 집부터 만들으라고?
I'm going to build one
for someone else?
옷을 기부하면 어때?
How about donating
some of your clothes?
바로 그거야!
안 입는 옷이 너무 많아
Oh, my God, that's perfect.
'Cause I have so many clothes
자리만 차지하고 있어서
I don't wear, and they're
just taking up space,
새옷을 사면
둘 자리가 없어
and I go shopping to buy more stuff
and I have no place to put it.
기부하면 해결되겠네
This will totally fix that.
남을 돕는 건?
What about helping people?
그러면서 돕는 거지
And helping people.
코코아 만들었어
Here's your cocoa.
- 일반 우유가 아닌 크림 우유?
- 응
- Oh, half and half instead of whole milk?
- Yes.
- 정확히 183도로 데웠고?
- 응
- Heated to precisely 183 degrees?
- Yes.
마시멜로는 7개?
Seven little marshmallows,
no more no less?
행운을 위해
하나 더 넣었어
You got one for good luck.
갑니다
(knocking)
I'll get it.
하나를 더 넣었다고?
One for good luck.
프린스턴에서 하는
수학이랑 비슷하네
Must be the kind of math
they do at Princeton.
Hey.
여긴 어쩐 일이야?
What are you doing here?
사과하러 왔어,
스테이플러로 고환을 찍고
I want to apologize for...
stapling your balls and...
옷을 벗겨
여자 탈의실에 가둔 거랑
...throwing you naked
in the girls' locker room,
바지 속에
앵무새를 넣은 것도
stuffing that parrot
down your pants.
이건 뭐야?
What's this word?
완하제
- "Laxative."
- Oh, right.
고2 파티였지
Junior prom.
못된 짓이였어
That was not cool, man.
정말 미안해
I am so, so sorry.
진심이야?
Really?
용서해주면 좋겠어
Yeah. I just hope
you can forgive me.
LEONARD:
Uh...
응
Yeah.
그러지 뭐
Sure, I guess.
넌 멋진 남자야
You're a beautiful guy.
고마워, 지미
Well, thanks, Jimmy.
이제 가야겠다
Okay, I got to go.
운전할 수 있겠어?
Are you okay to drive?
난 음주운전을 더 잘해
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I drive better drunk.
더 집중하게 되잖아
You know, it makes
you pay attention.
잠깐 들어와,
커피 만들어 줄게
No, no, no, come on in.
I'll make you a cup of coffee.
폐 끼치는 거 아냐?
- I wouldn't be imposing?
- No.
맞아
Yes.
쉘든, 이 상태로
보낼 수 없어
Sheldon, we can't
let him drive.
그럼 차 열쇠를
뺏고 내보내
Then take away his keys
and make him wander the streets
다른 주정뱅이들이랑
어울리겠네
with the other drunks.
내 친구들 기억하지?
You remember Sheldon
and Raj and Howard.
아니
Not really, no.
재밌지 않아, 레너드?
It's funny, huh, Leonard?
예전에는 네가 루저였는데
Back in school, I was the
winner and you were the loser.
이제는 그 반대야
And now we're reversed.
넌 성공했어
You're the winner.
성공한 사람이 이런
코코아를 내오다니
You'd think a winner could make
a decent cup of cocoa.
화장실 좀 써도 될까?
- You mind if I use your bathroom?
- Yeah, just back there.
예상 밖이네
How about that?
고등학교 때 괴롭히던
친구가 드디어 사과하다니
After all these years,
your big bad high school bully
finally apologizes.
사람들의 선한 본성을
다시 믿게되네
Yeah. It kind of rekindles
your faith
in the basic goodness of people.
좋은 생각이 있어
You know what
would be nice?
뭔데?
What's that?
우리를 괴롭힌 애들한테
메시지를 보내는 거야
As a symbolic gesture
to all the bullies who've
tormented us for years,
지미를 재워준다 하고
잠이 들면 죽여버리는 거지
we open our home to Jimmy and
once he's asleep we kill him.
좋은 생각이라 했지,
실제로 한다는 게 아냐
I said it would be nice--
I didn't say we should do it.
테레사 수녀 같아
I feel just like
Mother Teresa.
동정녀는 아니지만
Except for the virgin part.
오래 전에 벌어졌지
That ship sailed
a long time ago.
테레사 수녀라면
옷을 빨았을 거야
I think Mother Teresa would
have washed the clothes first.
세탁실이 계단으로
5층 떨어져있지 않았겠지
Yeah, well, I bet
her laundry room
wasn't down five flights
of stairs.
받는 것보다
주는 기쁨이 더 크네
You know, giving really
is better than receiving.
그냥 하는 말이라고
생각했었는데...
I used to think it was such a cliche,
but it seems to be the...
이런 청바지를
누가 버렸지
(gasps) Look at these cute jeans
someone just threw away.
기부한 거지
Donated.
부츠컷을 좋아하는
불쌍한 웨이트리스한테
Yes, to a poor waitress
who loves a boot cut.
페니
Penny.
나한테 너무 잘 어울려
Come on, they would
be so cute on me...
이 스웨터도 딱이다
They go great
with this sweater!
테레사 수녀라면...
I don't think
Mother Teresa...
오, 깜찍하다
Oh, that is adorable.
레너드
Leonard.
혹시 지미가 다시 물어보면
- Yeah.
- In case it comes up again,
폐 끼치는 거
맞다고 해줘
this right here
is an imposition.
어쩔 수 없었잖아
What was I supposed to do?
너무 취한 상태였어
He needed a place
to sleep it off.
넌 마음이 너무 약해
You're soft.
이 험악한 세상은
널 씹고 뱉어낼 거야
This world's going to chew
you up and spit you out.
(belches)
타코는 언제 먹었지?
When did I have tacos?
Morning, Jimmy.
타코 맞군
Oh, there it is, tacos.
과하게 마셨나봐
Man, I tied one on.
그런 것 같더라
Yeah, you did.
오랜만에 봐서 좋았어
So, uh, listen, it was
great to see you again.
그리고 사과도
잘 받았고
And thanks for
the apology.
무슨 사과?
What apology?
전에 괴롭힌 거에
대해 사과했잖아
For all the crappy stuff
you did to me in high school.
아직도 그거에 집착하냐?
Geez, you're still harping
on that?
이런 쪼잔한 자식
What a puss.
그건 내 프렌치토스트야
That's my French toast.
맛있네
It's good.
지지배가 요리를 꽤 하네
You really know your way
around a kitchen, Nancy.
'거봐'라고 말하진 않겠어
I'm not going to say
I told you so,
이미 죽일 기회를 놓쳤다
but we could have killed him.
지금 죽일 수도 있겠어
I might kill him right now.
다크 나이트가 도와줄게
The Dark Knight
has your back.
무섭지만 지켜주마
He's scared, but
he has your back.
지미, 이제 나가줘야겠다
Okay, Jimmy, it's time
for you to go.
이것 좀 먹고
Yeah, all right, let
me just finish this.
됐어, 당장 나가
No, you're done. I want you out
of my apartment right now.
잘했어, 로빈
Well said, Boy Wonder.
안 그럼 뭐?
Or what?
답하지 마,
속임수야
Don't answer that.
It's a trick question.
나도 경험해봤어
I speak from experience.
이젠 네가 무섭지 않아
I'm not afraid of you
anymore, Jimmy.
당장 나가라고
Now get out!
Uh-oh.
깡패한테 용감하게
맞서다니, 장하다
You did it, Leonard,
you stood up to your bully.
응, 기분이 좋네
Yeah, I feel pretty good
about myself.
안 잡히겠지?
You think we can
outrun him?
난 너보다
앞서기만 하면 돼
I don't need to outrun him,
I just need to outrun you.
느낌이 안 좋아
I don't feel
good about this.
그럼 차에서
시동 걸고 기다려
Then sit in the car
and keep it running.
새옷이 도착했네
You were right--
a whole new load.
나와라, 요가복
Come on, yoga top.
Mama needs a new yoga top.
베르나데트, 네 사이즈의
스웨이드 부츠야
Check it out, Bernadette,
suede boots, your size.
귀엽다
God, they're cute.
왜 이렇게 귀여운 거야?
Oh, why did they have
to be cute?
얘들아, 잠깐
Wait, wait, wait, guys,
just hang on.
경찰이 떴어?
What is it, the fuzz?
우리 좀 봐
Look at us.
무슨 짓이지
What are we doing?
난 널 따라서
범죄를 저지르려 했지
I was gleefully following you
to a life of crime,
감방 동료가 되는
그 날을 기대하며
looking forward to the day
we might be cell mates.
베르나데트는
가능할지 모르겠다
I don't know about Bernadette.
이러면 안돼,
다시 돌려주자
You know, this is wrong.
Let's put everything back.
여기
Here.
난 급식소에서
봉사하니까 괜찮아
It's okay, I serve soup
to poor people!
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==